Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Donald W. Taylor as dean, 1969-1976; Accession 2004-A-140
  - Yale College Fellowships (Box 21, Folder 971)
  - Yale Computer Center (Box 21, Folder 972)
  - Yale-In-China (Box 21, Folder 973)
  - Yale University Press (Box 21, Folder 974)
  - Yale Reports (Box 21, Folder 975)
  - Yale Volunteer Services Student Council (Box 21, Folder 976)
  - History of Graduate School (Box 21, Folder 977)
  - Housing Rentals and Meal Prices - Other Universities (Box 21, Folder 978)
  - Commencement, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 979)
  - Ad Hoc Committee - Astronomy, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 980)
  - Computer Science, Ad Hoc Committee (Box 21, Folder 981)
  - Culler Report - Humanities, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 982)
  - Elementary and Secondary Education - Executive Committee (Box 21, Folder 983)
  - Education, Ad Hoc Committee, 1965 February (Box 21, Folder 984)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Graduate Education for Women (Box 21, Folder 985)
  - Advisory Board - History of Science and Medicine (Box 21, Folder 986)
  - Ad Hoc Committee - Language Requirement, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 987)
  - Ad Hoc Committee - Linguistics, 1966 May (Box 21, Folder 988)
  - Logic and Communications Program (Box 21, Folder 989)
  - Oceanography - Ad Hoc Committee Materials (Box 21, Folder 990)
  - Pleistocene Geology - Ad Hoc Committee (Box 22, Folder 991)
  - Vertebrate Paleontology - Ad Hoc Committee (Box 22, Folder 992)
  - Woodstock-Yale Program (Box 22, Folder 993)
  - Deans' Annual Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 22, Folder 994)
  - Dean's Report (Box 22, Folder 995)
  - Budget Planning (Box 22, Folder 996)
  - Dean's Case Book (Box 22, Folder 997)
  - Dr. Leon A. Greenberg (Box 22, Folder 998)
  - HGS Inventory (Box 22, Folder 999)
  - NATO Professorship (Box 22, Folder 1000)
  - Yale University Police Department Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 1001)
  - Vassar-Yale Report, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 1002)
  - Grant and Contract Administration (Box 22, Folder 1003)
  - Honorary Degree Committee (Box 22, Folder 1004)
  - Honoraria (Box 22, Folder 1005)
  - Housekeeping Division Supervisors (Box 22, Folder 1006)
  - Humanities Ad Hoc Report Responses (Box 22, Folder 1007)
  - Humanities Advisory Committee (Box 22, Folder 1008)
  - Humanities - New Graduate Programs, Culler Committee Report, etc. (Box 22, Folder 1009)
  - Humanities Facilities, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1010)
  - Intensive Summer Studies Program - Harvard-Yale-Columbia, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1011)
  - Parking Authority - Yale (Box 22, Folder 1012)
  - Personnel Office (Box 22, Folder 1013)
  - Physical Sciences Advisory Committee (Box 22, Folder 1015)
  - Office of the President (Box 22, Folder 1016)
  - Office of the Provost, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 1017)
  - Retired Faculty - FAS Policies and Procedures (Box 22, Folder 1018)
  - Science Advisory Committee (Box 22, Folder 1019)
  - Secretary's Office (Box 22, Folder 1020)
  - Security Director's Office (Box 22, Folder 1021)
  - Singer Report (Box 22, Folder 1022)
  - Social Sciences Advisory Committee (Box 22, Folder 1023)
  - Committee on Operations and Uses in Social Sciences (Box 22, Folder 1024)
  - Harlan Smith - Letters of Reference [Restricted until Jan 1, 2050] (Box 22, Folder 1025)
  - Teacher Placement Office, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1026)
  - Treasurer's Office (Box 22, Folder 1027)
  - Ventures, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 1028)
  - Yale Honorary Degree Recipients, Sciences - Living (Box 22, Folder 1029)
  - Yale Map Laboratory (Box 22, Folder 1030)
  - Department of Administrative Sciences (Box 22, Folder 1031)
  - Departmental Annual Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 1032)
  - African Studies (Box 22, Folder 1033)
  - Afro-American Studies (Box 22, Folder 1034)
  - American Studies (Box 22, Folder 1035)
  - Department of Anatomy (Box 23, Folder 1036)
  - Department of Anthropology (Box 23, Folder 1037)
  - School of Art and Architecture (Box 23, Folder 1038)
  - Department of Astronomy (Box 23, Folder 1039)
  - Bingham Oceanographic Laboratory (Box 23, Folder 1040)
  - Program in Biometeorology (Box 23, Folder 1041)
  - Department of Biochemistry (Box 23, Folder 1042)
  - Department of Biology (Box 23, Folder 1043)
  - Center on Education (Box 23, Folder 1044)
  - Department of Chemistry (Box 23, Folder 1045)
  - Child Study Center (Box 23, Folder 1046)
  - Classics Department, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1047)
  - Comparative and European Studies Center (Ford) (Box 23, Folder 1048)
  - Department of Comparative Literature (Box 23, Folder 1049)
  - Computer Facilities and Services (Box 23, Folder 1050)
  - Committee on Computer Sciences (Box 23, Folder 1051)
  - Cowles Foundation (Box 23, Folder 1052)
  - Divinity School (Box 23, Folder 1053)
  - Divisional Advisory Committees (Box 23, Folder 1054)
  - East Asian Center (Ford) (Box 23, Folder 1055)
  - Department of East Asian Language and Literature, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 1056)
  - Economics (Box 23, Folder 1057)
  - Economics IFEA Program (Box 23, Folder 1058)
  - Economic Growth Center (Box 23, Folder 1059)
  - Department of Economic History, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1060)
  - Educational Administrators Fellowship Program (Box 23, Folder 1061)
  - Department of Engineering and Applied Science 1968 (Box 23, Folder 1062)
  - Department of English (Box 23, Folder 1063)
  - Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 1065)
  - Department of Forestry (Box 23, Folder 1066)
  - Forestry School Appointments Committee (Box 23, Folder 1067)
  - Department of French (Box 23, Folder 1068)
  - Geography Department, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1069)
  - Department of Geology (Box 23, Folder 1070)
  - Germanic Language and Literature (Box 23, Folder 1071)
  - Department of History (Box 24, Folder 1072)
  - Appointments Procedures - Proposed Salaries, Leave Policy, etc., 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1074)
  - Growth of Departments, 1960-1964 (Box 24, Folder 1075)
  - Committee on Master's Degree, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 1076)
  - New Trends in Graduate Training and Research in the Social Sciences (Box 24, Folder 1077)
  - NIH Foreign Student Financial Support (Box 24, Folder 1078)
  - Part Time Study in the Graduate School (Box 24, Folder 1079)
  - Ph.D. Degree Statistics - Length of Time for Completion (Box 24, Folder 1080)
  - Postdoctoral Research and Visiting Appointments - FAS (Box 24, Folder 1081)
  - Policies in Graduate Education - JPM/AGS Report (Box 24, Folder 1082)
  - Practicing Engineers Program (Box 24, Folder 1083)
  - Readmission After Draft - President's Directive (Box 24, Folder 1084)
  - Recruiting Graduate Students (Box 24, Folder 1085)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Social Sciences (Box 24, Folder 1086)
  - Postdoctorals in Social Sciences - Draft, JPM, 1968 August 6 (Box 24, Folder 1087)
  - Uncertainty in the Graduate School (Box 24, Folder 1088)
  - History of Art (Box 24, Folder 1089)
  - History of Science and Medicine (Box 24, Folder 1090)
  - History of the Theater (Box 24, Folder 1091)
  - Human Relations Area Files (Box 24, Folder 1092)
  - Italian (Box 24, Folder 1093)
  - International Relations (Box 24, Folder 1094)
  - Latin American Studies (Box 24, Folder 1095)
  - Law School (Box 24, Folder 1096)
  - Department of Linguistics (Box 24, Folder 1097)
  - Department of Mathematics (Box 24, Folder 1098)
  - Medical School (Box 24, Folder 1099)
  - Department of Medieval Studies (Box 24, Folder 1100)
  - Microbiology (Box 24, Folder 1101)
  - Molecular Biophysics (Box 24, Folder 1102)
  - History of Music Department (Box 24, Folder 1103)
  - Music Theory (Box 24, Folder 1104)
  - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 24, Folder 1105)
  - Coordinating Committee on Oceanography (Box 24, Folder 1106)
  - School of Nursing (Box 24, Folder 1107)
  - Old Testament Program, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1108)
  - Peabody Museum, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 1109)
  - Pharmacology (Box 24, Folder 1110)
  - Philosophy (Box 24, Folder 1111)
  - Department of Physics (Box 24, Folder 1112)
  - Physiology (Box 24, Folder 1113)
  - Political Science (Box 24, Folder 1115)
  - Office of Political Studies (Box 24, Folder 1116)
  - Department of Psychology (Box 24, Folder 1117)
  - Religious Studies (Box 25, Folder 1118)
  - Department of Religious Studies Announcement (Also Vita of Faculty) (Box 25, Folder 1119)
  - Religious Studies Faculty Council (Box 25, Folder 1120)
  - Russian and East European Studies (Box 25, Folder 1121)
  - Russian Studies - MA Program (Box 25, Folder 1122)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 25, Folder 1123)
  - Institute of Social Sciences (Box 25, Folder 1124)
  - Department of Sociology (Box 25, Folder 1125)
  - Southeast Asia Studies (Box 25, Folder 1126)
  - Spanish (Box 25, Folder 1127)
  - Department of Statistics (Box 25, Folder 1128)
  - Transportation (Box 25, Folder 1129)
  - University Health Department (Box 25, Folder 1130)
  - Joint Board Meeting Agendas, 1964-1968 (Box 25, Folder 1131)
  - HGS Tower Assignments, 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 1132)
  - HGS Office Assignments, 1956-1966 (Box 25, Folder 1133)
  - Committee Lists (Graduate School) (Box 25, Folder 1134)
  - Board of Permanent Officers, Yale College and Graduate School - Old Lists (Box 25, Folder 1135)
  - Directors of Graduate Study Lists (Old) (Box 25, Folder 1136)
  - New IBM Charging Accounts and Instructions (Box 25, Folder 1137)
  - Monthly Deposits - Graduate School Accounts, 1966-1967 (Box 25, Folder 1138)
  - Admissions and FPS Policy, 1964-1966 (Box 25, Folder 1139)
  - Qualifications for Advanced Study (Box 25, Folder 1140)
  - Travel Vouchers (Box 25, Folder 1141)
  - JPM Government Printing Office Requests, Yale Library Requests, etc. (Box 25, Folder 1142)
  - Department Regulations - JPM NY Times Letter (Box 25, Folder 1143)
  - Education at Yale - Report (Box 25, Folder 1144)
  - Organization of Appointments Committees (Faculty) (Box 25, Folder 1145)
  - Financial Support of Graduate Studies - FPS Policy Committee (Box 25, Folder 1146)
  - Financial Needs Report - Graduate School (Box 25, Folder 1147)
  - Foreign Student Financial Assistance, 1963-1964 (Box 25, Folder 1148)
  - Functions of the Graduate School - JPM (Box 25, Folder 1149)
  - Grades and the Graduate School - Article, JPM, 1967 May 10 (Box 25, Folder 1150)
  - Graduate Student Teaching Appointments - Yale College and Graduate School (Box 25, Folder 1151)
  - The Educational System of the U.S. (Box 25, Folder 1152)
  - Chart I, 1887-1964 (Box 25, Folder 1153)
  - AGS Speech, 1968 October (Box 25, Folder 1154)
  - Dean's Report Material, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 1155)
  - Dean's Report, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 1156)
  - Dean's Report (Box 26, Folder 1157)
  - Leaves of Absence, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1158)
  - Leaves of Absence Letters, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 1159)
  - Budget - Graduate School, Expense Sheets, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 1160)
  - Dean Discovery Fund 8700-1935-1976825, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1161)
  - Graduate School Alumni Fund 8700-1935-1966402, 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 1162)
  - Budget - Graduate School, Expense Sheets, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1163)
  - Budget Material, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 1164)
  - Expenses - Travel (Box 26, Folder 1165)
  - Graduate School Association - Past (Box 26, Folder 1166)
  - Degree Committees Notice, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 1168)
  - Executive Committee - Graduate School, 1963-1967 (Box 26, Folder 1169)
  - University Council Reports Including Graduate School, 1963- (Box 26, Folder 1170)
  - Former Staff, 1971-1976 (Box 26, Folder 1171 - 1174)
  - The Graduate School Alumni Association (Box 26, Folder 1178)
  - Stanford Laboratory Book (Box 27, Folder 1181)
  - Effects of Observation Cost on Sequential Search Behavior - Amnon Report (Box 27, Folder 1182)
  - Study of Postdoctoral Education (Box 27, Folder 1183)
  - A program to Play Chess End Games - B.J. Huberman (Box 27, Folder 1184)
  - Visual Signal Detection as a Function of Sequential Variability of Simultaneous Speech - J.S. Antrobus (Box 27, Folder 1185)
  - Exploring Man's Imaginative World - J.L. Singer (Box 27, Folder 1186)
  - An Experimental Study of Some Relationships Between Daydreaming and Anxiety - J.L. Singer (Box 27, Folder 1187)
  - A Factor-Analytic Study of Daydreaming and Conceptually-Related Cognitive and Personality Variables: Items on Daydream and Columbia Attention Battery Scales - J.L. Singer, et al (Box 27, Folder 1188)
  - The Moon Illusion, I and II - L. Kaufman et al (Box 27, Folder 1189)
  - Letters - DWT (Box 27, Folder 1190)
  - The Moon Illusion - L. Kaufman et al (Box 27, Folder 1191)
  - The Process of Conflict Resolution - J.E. Durkin et al (Box 27, Folder 1192)
  - Quantum Electronics, and Surprise in Development of Technology - C.H. Townes (Box 27, Folder 1193)
  - A Quantitative Measure for Programmed Instruction - J.G. Holland (Box 27, Folder 1194)
  - Cooperation in the Prisoner's Dilemma Game I: The Effects of Assymetric Payoff, Information andExplicit Communication - R.G. Swensson (Box 27, Folder 1195)
  - Some Experimental Studies of Kpelle Quantitative Behavior - M. Cole et al (Box 27, Folder 1196)
  - Yale College and Yale Graduate School - A Report Prepared for the New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, Inc. (Box 27, Folder 1197)
  - Registrar's Office Material (Box 27, Folder 1198)
  - Preliminary Edition - Bibliography of Games and Situations - M.G. Holmen (Box 27, Folder 1199)
  - Fair Labor Standard Act (Box 27, Folder 1200 - 1202)
  - Fair Labor Standard Act Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1203)
  - Internal Operating Manual - Graduate School (Box 27, Folder 1204)
  - Fair Labor Standard Act Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 1205)
  - Recruitment, Selection, Training, Appraisal, Compensation, and Motivation of Professional Personnel in McKinsey and Company (Box 28, Folder 1206)
  - Fair Labor Standard Act Reports
    - 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1207)
    - 1969 (Box 28, Folder 1208)
    - 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1209)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 1210)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 1211)
  - Former Staff, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 1212)
  - Time Sheets, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 1213)
  - Committee on Academic Computing (Box 29, Folder 1214)
  - The Evaluation of Teaching - E.R. Guthrie (Box 29, Folder 1215)
  - Psychology Department (Box 29, Folder 1216)
  - Faculty Research Grant Applications, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1217)
  - Report of the Committee on Academic Computing (Box 29, Folder 1218)
  - Augmented Dwarfs (Box 29, Folder 1219)
  - Dwarfs (Box 29, Folder 1220)
- Records of Keith Stewart Thomson as dean, 1979-1986; Accession 2004-A-143
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - Outside Readers for Dissertations, 1971- (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Fund Contributions, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Leaves of Absence
    - 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Requests, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Letters, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Appointment Requests - Administrative Sciences (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Afro-American Studies (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - American Studies (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Appointment Requests - Anthropology (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Appointment Requests, Corporation Vote - Astronomy (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Department of Biology (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Appointment Requests, Corporation Vote - Chemistry (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Appointment Requests, Corporation Vote - Classical Languages and Literatures (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Appointment Requests, Corporation Vote - Comparative Literature (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Computer Science (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Appointment Requests, Corporation Vote - Economics (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Appointment Requests, Corporation Vote - East and South Asian Languages and Literatures (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Department of Engineering and Applied Science (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - English (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Forestry (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - French (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Geography (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Geology (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - History (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - History of Art (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - History of Science and Medicine (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Human Genetics (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - ISPS (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Italian (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Linguistics (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Mathematics (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Music (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Near Eastern Languages (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Organization and Management (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Peabody Museum (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Pharmacology (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Physics (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Political Science (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Philosophy (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Physiology (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Psychology (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Department of Religious Studies (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Russian Studies (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Spanish (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Southeast Asia Studies (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Sociology (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Department of Statistics (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Office of Teacher Training (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Professors - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - A (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - B (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - C (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - D (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - E (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - F (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - G (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - H (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - I (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - J (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - K (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - L (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - M (Includes Mc and Mac) (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - N (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - O (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - P (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Q (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - R (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - S (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - T (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - U (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - V (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - W (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - XYZ (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Engineering and Applied Science (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Research Appointments
    - Astronomy (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Biology (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Chemistry (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Economics (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Engineering and Applied Sciences (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - English (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Geology and Geophysics (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - History (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - ISPS (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Mathematics (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - M and B (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Physics (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Political Science (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Psychology (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Religious Studies (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Sociology (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Statistics (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Memoranda
    - Admission to Candidacy and Leaves of Absence, 1973 May 7 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Financial Aid to Students Admitted to the Yale Graduate School in the Fall of 1973-1974, 1973 March 15 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Request for Nominations for Prize Teaching Fellowships, 1973 April 26 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Vote by Mail on Recommendations with Respect to: Admission to Candidacy and Leaves of Absence, 1973 April 22 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Financial Aid During the Summer of 1973, 1973 April 12 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Financial Aid for Current Students, 1973 April 6 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Admissions and Financial Aid for 1973-1974, 1973 March 12 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Eligibility of Those Holding Fellowships, Traineeships, …for Appointment as Teaching Fellow During 1973-1974, 1973 March 9 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Prize Dissertation Fellowships, 1973 March 8 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Comparison of Applications Received (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Memoranda
    - Admissions and Financial Aid for 1973-1974, 1973 February 26 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Applications Recommended for Admission, 1973 January 29 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Increased Availability of Yale National Direct Student Loans (NDSL), 1973 January 8 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Copy for the Graduate School Bulletin, 1973 January 2 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Admissions and Financial Aid for 1973-1974, 972 December 14 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Appointments Committee Procedures, 1972 December 12 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - To Members of the Faculty of the Graduate School, 1972 December 11 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Length of Time for Beginning of Graduate Study at Yale to Submission of Dissertation (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Table - Number of Faculty Members Whose Primary Appointment was in a Department Which in 1972-1973 is in Arts and Sciences, 1972 December 11 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Memoranda
    - Admissions for 1972-1973, Changes over Eleven Years in the Size of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1972 November 6 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Stipends for Assistants in Research Whose Compensation Qualifies for Exemption from Income Tax, 1972 November 3 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Eligibility of Those Holding Outside Fellowships…for Appointment as Teaching Fellows, 1972 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Analysis of Students Declining Admission in 1972-1973, GAPSFAS, 1972 October 5 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Employment of Assistants in Instruction, 1972 September 1 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Long-term Loans, 1972 August 10 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - Decision to Participate in the Contingent Repayment Plan…, 1972 August 9 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Long-term Loans, 1972 August 8 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - The Contingent Repayment Plan and Procedure for Making Application, 1972 August 7 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - Recommended Actions with Respect to Interdepartmental Programs in the Graduate School (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - Ad Hoc Increases in Teaching Honoraria 1971-1972, 1972 May 3 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Eligibility of Those Holding Fellowships for Appointment as Teaching Fellow or Part-time Acting Instructor, 1972 April 24 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Request for Nominations for Prize Teaching Fellowships, 1972 April 22 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Financial Aid and Teaching Appointments, 1972 April 12 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Financial Aid During the Summer of 1972, 1972 April 11 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Policies and Procedures Governing the Appointment of Graduate Students to Teach…, 1972 April 10 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Amount of Supplementary Stipend for Teaching 1971-1972, 1972 April 6 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Financial Aid to Students Admitted - Fall 1972-1973, 1972 March 15 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - Financial Aid for Current Students, 1972 March 8 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Executive Meeting, 1972 February 18 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Possible Alternative System for Teaching Appointments…, 1972 February 17-18 (Box 6, Folder 147 - 148)
    - A Study of Employment of 1970-1971 Doctorates, 1972 February 4 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Increase for 1972-1973 in Availability to Graduate Students…, 1972 February 3 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Admissions and Financial Aid for 1972-1973, 1972 January 11 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Applicants Recommended for Admission, 1972 January 28 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Review of Interdepartmental Programs, 1972 January 5 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Current Students' Financial Aid Applications, 1971 December 23 (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Mar 15 Deadline…, 1971 December 8 (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Increased Availability…, 1971 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Part-time Study in the Graduate School (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Reestablishment of M.A. and M.S. Degrees, 1971 November 13 (Box 6, Folder 158)